(忆往昔)
[咒语]
不要
Don't.
你小子去哪了  小卡
Where the hell are you, Cass?
我没事
I'm fine.
你听上去不像没事
You don't sound okay.
你也解决不了我的问题
What I have, you can't help me.
告诉萨姆
Please tell Sam...
罗威娜拿着《诅咒之书》和法典逃跑了
Rowena escaped with The Book of the Damned and the codex.
她的名字是阿玛拉
Her name is Amara.
我们是联系在一起的  迪恩
We're bound, Dean.
我们会永远联系在一起
We'll always be bound.
你帮助过我
You helped me.
我们永远都会帮助彼此
We will always help each other.
阿玛拉应该就是黑暗
I think Amara is the Darkness.
有意思
Interesting.
不管那房子里的是什么
Whatever's in that house,
我能嗅到它辐射出来的法力
I can taste the power radiating from it.
它很古老  很深
It's old, deep...
很黑暗
dark.
你去哪
Where you going?
去看那个吃灵魂的孩子
To see the child that eats souls.
别碰她
Stay away from her!
我想要那个孩子  而我总能如愿以偿
I want that child, and I get what I want.
天呐  瞧瞧你长成了这么个小可爱
My, haven't you grown into a sweet young thing?
我感到咒语陷得越来越深
I feel the spell just cutting deeper and deeper,
我想抵抗
and I'm trying to fight it.
我尽力抵抗的
I'm trying...
救救我
Help me.
(如今)
要叫所有人知道我们的厉害
And they shall know us far and wide
惧怕我们
and fear us.
我们就叫
And we shall be known as...
超大巫师团
the Mega Coven!
Mega Coven.
因为我们比大巫师团大
See because it's greater than Grand Coven,
所以不叫大巫师团  叫超大
so it's not grand, it's mega.
是超大巫师团  你们没听懂吧
It's the Mega Coven. I don't think you're followin'.
我们为什么要加入你这个巫师团啊
And why ever would we join you in such a thing?
因为你们那个大巫师团已经没救了
Because that grand coven of yours is obsolete.
你还不明白吗
Don't you see?
自从女祭司奥莉薇特消失后它就四分五裂了
And utterly falling apart since the High Priestess Olivette disappear.
我们听说那可能跟你有关
Wich we hear you may have had a hand in.
闲言碎语罢了
Idle gossip.
少说废话了  罗威娜
Cut the crap, Rowena.
你只是想寻求保护  躲避温家那对猎人兄弟
You're just looking for protection from the hunter Winchesters
和其他你数目众多的敌人
and all the rest of your many enemies.
亲爱的  你没胆也没能力做到这事
And, honey, you don't have the guts or the chops to pull this off.
所以咱们就别自欺欺人了
So let's not kid ourselves.
是吗
Really?
恰巧  我杀了地狱之王
It so happens, I killed the king of hell.
我亲儿子  地狱之王
My own son, the king of hell,
还是控制了一个天使去动手
and compelled an angel to do it.
胆量  能力  要我说我都有
Guts? Chops? I'd say that qualifies.
我有个朋友昨天才跟克劳力做了笔交易
I have a friend, who cut a deal with Crowley only yesterday.
他看上去不像死了呢
Crowley didn't look so dead.
什么
What?
你还像以前一样想入非非  我们走了
You're as delusional as ever. We'll be going.
想入非非
Delusional?
我们走着瞧吧
We'll see.
[咒语]
他没死啊
He lives?
[邪恶力量 第11季第3集]
最后一个邻居也问过了  跟其他的一样
So, that was the last of the neighbours, just like the rest.
迪恩
Dean?
Dean!
嗯
Yeah.
没事吧
You okay?
嗯
Yeah.
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
那么没有发现喽
So you're saying we got nothing.
婴儿失踪那天
No one saw anything unusual
没有人看到房子那里有任何异常情况
going on at the house the day the baby disappeared.
如果真的是黑暗的话
If this is truly the Darkness we're talking about,
它就不是个婴儿  而是定时炸弹了
it's more of a time bomb than a baby.
但它也还是个婴儿吧
Yeah, but it is still a baby, right?
我看到的黑暗是个成年人
I mean the Darkness I saw was an adult,
它还得长大呢
so it still has to grow up.
黑暗有无限的力量
The Darkness is almost infinite power.
我不知道这个情况下"长大"意味着什么
I'm not sure what "Growing up" means in this case.
上帝以前收拾过这东西一次  是吧
Well, God kick this thing's ass once before, right?
是啊  如果他能把鸡尾酒放下
Yeah, it'd be nice if he put down the Mai Tai
-来上班就好了  -别指望了
- and show up for work. - I wouldn't count on it.
他可能就在附近  比我们想的要近呢
It's possible he's around. Closer than we think, you know?
你为什么那么说
What makes you say that?
我觉得他走掉时就已经明确表达了态度了
I believe he made a fairly definitive statement when he walked away.
抱歉拴着你  小卡
Sorry about those, Cass.
我们确定你的问题之前
Till we know what's going on with you,
你还指不定能干出什么来
you're still a bit of a wild card, you know.
我也不想说  但你们都清楚我们可能需要谁
I hate to point this out, but you both know who we might need
来帮忙应付黑暗
to help deal with the Darkness.
别说出来
Don't even say it.
他是上帝的书记官  他什么事都听到了
He was God's scribe. He did hear about everything.
这跟说出来有什么区别
That's just like saying it.
小卡  你没事吧
Cass you all right, pal?
是咒语
It's the spell.
我们还希望你的天使体制能扛过去呢
We were hoping your angel wiring would fight it off
至少能有所减缓
Or...slow it down at least.
看来我只是跟人类的反应不同而已
It appears I simply respond differently from humans.
如果你是人类  你这会儿都死了
If you were you human, you'd be gone.
而在你身上  这东西越陷越深
With you, it's like it's digging deeper.
罗威娜是唯一能解除咒语的人
You know, Rowena's the only one who can remove it.
我们在尽一切努力找她了
We're doing everything to find her, okay?
但目前为止毫无进展
But so far, we got nothing.
情况越来越糟了
Well, it's getting worse.
是  陛下  我的手下确定
Yes, majesty, my operative is certain.
您母亲已经找到了
Your mother has been found.
那行动吧
Then move.
灭了那个狡诈的贱人
Annihilate the treacherous bitch.
她的学习进展飞快
She's making impressive progress in her studies,
毕竟几天前她还穿着尿布呢
considering just days ago she was in diapers.
看好她
Watch her.
绝不能让她与宫外的人接触
She speaks to no one outside the court.
如果她的法力有我想的一半的强
If she's half as powerful as I think she is,
我一定要她站在我这边
I want her on my team.
阿玛拉这名字挺好听的  是您给起的吗
Amara's a pretty name. Did you name her?
是可爱的珍娜那么喊她
That's what the lovely Jenna called her,
但阿玛拉却吸食了她的灵魂
Just before Amara sucked out her soul.
我们现在让她看什么呢
What do we have her watching now?
希特勒纽伦堡演讲
Hitler's Nuremberg speeches.
翻译好的
We had them translated.
阿玛拉  亲爱的
Amara, sweetie?
你如果想可以休息一下的
You can take a little break if you like.
保姆说你学得很好
Nanny said you're doing very well with your schooling.
我希望你在新家待的开心
I want you to be happy in your new home.
不管你要什么  不管什么时候要
Whatever you want, whenever you want it,
你说就是了
you just have to ask.
我只想要你保护我  别让他抓到我
I just want you to save me, from him.
上帝吗
From God?
他对我的宝贝姑娘很坏  是不是
He's been very mean to my little girl, hasn't he?
-他骗了我  -他很狡猾
- He tricked me. - He's a wily one.
他把我关了起来
He sealed me away.
他究竟怎么做到的
And how exactly did he manage that?
我不想说
I don't want to talk about it.
当然
Of course.
你很幸运  我是个国王
You're a very lucky girl. I'm a king.
要说有谁能保护你不受那个无赖神祇的伤害
And if anyone can protect you from that rascally deity,
就是我了
it is I.
谢谢你
Thank you.
"谢谢你  克劳力叔叔"
"Thank you, uncle Crowley."
"怎么会这样"  我一直在自问
"How did this happen?" I kept asking myself.
巫术本是骄傲大胆的职业
Witchcraft was a proud and adventurous calling.
但大巫师团却容许它堕落崩溃
But the Grand Coven let it collapse in disgrace.
女巫们懦弱地隐藏于黑暗之中
Cowardly witches hiding in shadows.
毕竟当年我们被成千上万地烧死绞死啊
Well, we were being burned or hung by the thousands.
这抑制了我们的热情
It put a lid on our enthusiasm.
胡说  那是领导不力
Nonsense. Poor leadership.
我们族类应该得到复兴
Our people deserve a renaissance.
我在找精英中的精英
And I'm looking for the best of the best
离开大巫师团
to leave the Grand Coven
加入我
and join me
我的...
in...the...
超大巫师团
Mega Coven.
你们听到了吧
You hear what I said, right?
天呐  看看这都几点了
My...look at the time.
我说过我手里有
Did I mention I have in my possession
《诅咒之书》吗
The Book of the Damned?
是的  疯修女艾格尼丝写的
Aye, written by crazy sister Agnes herself,
写在自己的皮肉上
on her own flesh.
它蕴含的秘密让我成为了自然之力  姑娘们
Its secrets are making me a force of nature, girls.
自然之力啊
A force of nature.
你愿把这些秘密
And you'd share these secrets
与超大巫师团共享吗
with the...Mega Coven?
我一向乐于施于
I've always been a giver.
我能做军官吗
Is there a chance I could be an officer?
我在大巫师团就做到了纠察长
In the Grand Coven, I never made it past sergeant-at-arms.
你都想不到自己能得到怎样的好处
You have no idea the rewards headed your way.
[咒语]
克劳力  快接啊
Come on, Crowley, pick up.
我都给你留了十数条留言了
I've left you a dozen messages.
他为什么不接电话
Why isn't he answering the phone?
因为他是个混蛋  这都不是新闻了
Because he's a dick, and that's not breaking news.
他肯定盯着罗威娜呢吧
He's gotta have Rowena in his sights, right?
她可是想杀他啊
I mean, she did try to take him out.
他不会把罗威娜给我们的
He's not gonna deliver Rowena to us
就为了让她解除咒语
just so she can lift the spell.
他会宁可让咒语在我身上肆虐
He'd rather let it do whatever it's gonna do to me.
-他肯定有所图谋  -当然
- He's gotta be up to something. - Yeah.
再说一次  不是新闻了
Again, not breaking news.
梅塔特隆也不见踪影
Metatron is also off the grid.
他在密苏里州布莱恩偷了你的车  是吧
He stole your car in Blaine, Missouri, right?
嗯
Yeah.
嗯  没有任何跟一辆破烂
Yeah, uh, no accidents, incidents, violations,
78款大陆马克5有关的车祸
or anything remotely interesting involving
事故  违规或有趣事件
a crappy '78 continental mark v.
你觉得那车很破吗
You think it's crappy?
旁观者清
Eye of the beholder.
嗯
Yeah.
他避世几世纪
A shut-in for centuries,
之前是上帝的书记官
former scribe of God.
按理说不该很会开车
You wouldn't think he would be a good driver.
这样吧  我找找他可能去的地方
You know what? I'll look for unusual occurrences
有没有什么异常事件
at places he might hang out.
小卡
Cass?
梅塔特隆可能去的地方
Places Metatron might hang out.
他喜欢华夫饼
I mean, he loves waffles.
试试有华夫饼的地方吧
You could try places that have those.
好吧  那么整个国家的每家餐馆喽
Okay, so, every restaurant in the entire country.
小卡
Cass?
小卡  小卡
Cass? Cass, hey!
没事  放松
Easy! Easy!
小卡
Cass?!
Cass?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
跟什么相比
Relative to what?
你知道自己在哪吗  今天哪天
You know where you are? What's the date?
地球
Earth.
据时之初已经过了几十亿年
Several billion years from the beginning.
起来吧  伙计
Come on, buddy.
起来吧
Come on.
我好像在一个搅拌机里
It's like I was... inside a blender
还设成了做番茄酱果泥的档
that was set to puree for a tomato salsa.
你是那只番茄喽
And you're the tomato?
在这个比喻里  是的
In this analogy, yes.
嗯
Yeah.
小卡  刚刚怎么回事
Cass, what was that?
你吓死我们俩了
You scared the crap out of us.
我大部分时间都昏过去了
I blacked out for a lot of it.
但是我
But I...
我不知道  我没招架住
I don't know. It overwhelmed me.
我控制不了
I-I couldn't control it.
我们把他扶起来吧  起来
Let's get him up. Come on, come on.
好了
Here you go.
-我们得找到那个女巫  -嗯
- We gotta find that witch. - Yeah.
-我能帮什么忙  -不不
- What can I do to help? - No, no, no,
你坐好  休息一下
You just, uh, sit there and take a breather,
让自己恢复一下
try and put yourself back together.
好
Okay.
我尽力吧  但是
I'll do my best. It's...
有那些声音好困难
It's difficult with these voices.
还有幻音了
Now there are voices?
这些声音叫你伤害别人吗
Are these voices telling you to hurt someone?
不  伙计们  我能听到天使无线电
No. Guys, I'm... I'm hearing angel radio.
说话的人很多  他们
It's a lot of chatter. They're...
他们逃走之后  他们一直在找我
They've been looking for me ever since I escaped,
还在满世界找罪犯
as well as scouring the earth for the perp.
就是"犯罪者"的俚语
It's slang for "Perpetrator."
嗯  多谢解释
Yeah, thank you.
在找哪个特定的"罪犯"吗
Um, a-any..."perp" in particular?
梅塔特隆
Metatron.
他们投入了双倍人力找他
They're doubling the effort to find him, so...
我们如果想找到他  就得赶快了
if we need to get hold of him, we better do it soon.
嗯  别让上帝小分队抢先了
Yeah, before the God squad does.
好吧  重要的事先做
All right, well, first thing's first.
听听这个  可能有谱
Listen to this. May be something here.
丹佛一家埃塔咖啡厅中  三位女顾客的
Uh, in Denver, three women were at this Café Elta,
服务员  无缘无故地
when their waiter, for no apparent reason,
刺死了其中一人
stabbed and killed one.
一人生还  第三名消失不见
One survived and the third vanished
而家具都自行绕着她移动开了
after furniture seemed to slide around by itself.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
埃塔咖啡厅的调查谁负责
Hi, who's your lead on the Café Elta investigation?
(埃塔咖啡厅发生凶杀案)
你似乎很困惑
You look confused.
有烦恼
Troubled.
上帝把我关起来后创造了这么多
God did all of this after he locked me away.
我不知道有这么多
I didn't know it was so much.
都是为满足他自己的自大
All for his own ego.
不管他创造了什么
And no matter what he made,
都不是他那么对我们的借口
that doesn't excuse what he did to us.
我知道
I know.
阿玛拉
Amara...
你得专注于我们的目标
You must stay fixed on our purpose.
就连我们也不能撤销已经发生的事
Even we cannot undo what's already done.
但随着你成长起来  愈发强大
But as you grow and become stronger,
你将明白你真正的使命
your true destiny will become clear to you.
你长大就会成为我
I am what you are becoming.
我们比上帝更加强大
And we are mightier than God.
还没睡呢
Not in bed yet?
是啊  快了
Not yet. Soon.
还在学习呢  真乖
Working on your studies. Good girl.
学到什么有意思的了吗
Learning anything interesting?
好像有
I think so.
天堂情况不妙吗
Pretty bad in heaven?
嗯  楼下怎么样
Yep. How 'bout downstairs?
别跟我提
Yeah, don't get me started.
警报作响了吗
Alarms go off?
你都不会相信
You wouldn't believe.
是啊  我们也是
I know, right? Us, too.
有什么变了
Something's changed.
有什么来了
Something's here.
很大
It's big.
跟上帝一样大  跟路西法一样大
Big as God. Big as Lucifer.
你们那边采取什么行动了吗
They doing anything about it on your end?
完全没有
Zip.
楼上呢
How 'bout upstairs?
一切照旧
Ah, business as usual.
按理说该有个什么行政命令之类的  但是
You'd think there'd be an executive order, but...
国王躲起来不知干什么呢
The king's holed up doing who knows what.
汉娜死后
After Hannah died,
天堂就一团乱了
Heaven's pretty much been a suck sandwich.
知道谁受苦吗  我们这种基层的
You know who gets squeezed? It's grunts like us.
是啊  就打个卡  有你没你都行
Yeah, punch a clock, you're expendable.
我们两家一向是对头
You know, our two operations will always butt heads.
当初设置就是如此
That's the set up.
但是这事
But this?
我们可能会丢了工作
We could be out of work.
是啊  我们被干倒  它掌权
Yeah. We get knocked out, it takes over.
总得有人做点什么
Someone's gotta do something.
-谁  -是啊
- Someone? - Yeah.
如果管理层不作为  就得靠小人物了
If management won't, it's up to the little guy.
嗯  有道理
Yeah. I hear ya.
敬人民当权  朋友
Power to the people, my friend.
也不算人民啦
Well, not actually people.
你知道我什么意思的
You know what I mean.
-警局  -谢谢
- Sheriff's Station- Thanks.
-探员  请  -交给我们吧  嗯
- Agents, here you go. - We got it. Yep.
你好
Hello.
女士们共进午餐出了岔子
So, ladies lunch goes south
一名浑身硫磺味儿的服务员
when a waiter, who reeks of sulfur,
持刀袭击了你们  杀死一人
attacks with a blade, killing one of you,
而请你吃饭的红发女人
while the redhead who invited you
大喊了一句拉丁文  就无影无踪了
yells something in latin, disappears,
而家具则叠成了一摞  是这样吧
and the furniture forms a pile. That about right?
知道一个恶魔为什么要袭击三个女巫吗
Any idea why a demon would wanna attack three witches?
我不知道你在说什么
I-I don't know what you're talking about.
嗯  服务员被一个
Right. The waiter was possessed
企图行刺罗威娜的恶魔附身了
by a demon assassin who was gunning for Rowena,
因为她企图杀她儿子克劳力
since she tried to kill her son Crowley,
而他恰好是地狱之王
who just so happens to be the King of Hell.
我为什么觉得你们不像警察说的  是联调局的
Why do I think you're not F.B.I. like the police said?
直说吧
Let's cut to it.
警方说你吓得
The cops say that you're so scared,
不想离开这里了
you don't wanna leave here.
你是该害怕
Well, you should be,
因为克劳力不仅想要罗威娜
'cause Crowley's not only going after Rowena,
他也不会放过所有她的女巫朋友
he's going after every witch that she hangs with.
-我不是女巫  -你当然是
- I-I'm no witch. - Sure, you are.
你朋友罗威娜  她在为新巫师团招募吧
And your pal Rowena, she's recruiting a new coven.
你不能那么做  我有权利的
You can't do this. I have rights.
我还有假警徽呢
And I have a fake badge.
看啊
Look at this.
鸡骨
Chicken bones.
巫术袋
Hex bags.
五芒星
A pentagram.
还要说
Still sticking with, uh...
不是女巫吗
not a witch?
[咒语]
你说完你想说的之前
Listen, before you finish what you're about to say,
要知道只有我们
know that we are the only thing
挡在你和克劳力的刺客之间
between you and Crowley's ninjas.
我又没想伤害他
But I didn't try to hurt him.
我是个小人物  我什么都不是
I mean, I am nobody. I-I'm worse than nobody.
我是小人物的远方表亲
I-I'm nobody's third cousin
从不会被请去吃饭
who doesn't even get invited to dinner.
我们不管
We don't care.
我们只想知道罗威娜在哪
We just need to know where Rowena is.
我不知道
I have no idea.
但你会占卜吧
But you do know how to scry, is that right?
占卜  什么东西
Scry? What's that?
就是那个意思  定位咒
Exactly what you know it is. A locating spell.
你们女巫用水晶  棱镜
When you witches use crystals and then prisms
和镜子占卜你想找的人的影像
and mirrors to divine images of who you're trying to find.
我们想找到罗威娜
We're trying to get our hands on Rowena.
她如果死了
Okay, now with her out of the picture,
克劳力就没必要追着你不放
Crowley has no reason to go after you.
懂了吗
You got it?
我没带水晶
I don't have my crystals.
那么
Well...
这个也能行吧
This ought to work, huh?
我关灯
I'll get the light.
[咒语]
我看到她了
I see her.
她在收拾东西
She's packing a bag.
阿玛拉
Amara.
我有礼物给你
I have a gift for you.
准确说  是两份礼物
Two, actually.
那是血吗
Is that...blood?
可能是吧
Probably.
还有
And...
(跳跳大叔)
抱歉我这么虎妈
You have to forgive me for being the tiger mom,
但用书籍丰富头脑永远不嫌早
but it's never too soon to improve your mind with books.
是啊
Agreed,
但我更喜欢保姆给我的这本
but I like the one nanny gave me more.
但丁的《神曲:地狱篇》
"Dante's inferno"?
还是原版意大利文的
In the original Italian.
保姆还教你其他我们世界的东西了吗
Has nanny been teaching you other things about our world?
教了一些
Some.
不是很和谐啊  是吧
Doesn't work very well, does it?
上帝就这样  根本没想清楚
That's God for you. Not really thought out.
什么大爆炸的  就是大失败
The whole big bang thing? More of a big bust.
嘭  呯
I mean, boom, bang,
繁星  进化  泰勒·斯威夫特
stars, evolution, Taylor Swift.
我猜换你就不会这么做吧
I'm guessing you'd have done things differently.
当然了
I sure will.
我考虑过很久了
I've had a lot of time to think it through.
有什么具体我们可以期待的吗
Any...specifics that we have to look forward to?
我饿了
I'm hungry.
当然
Of course.
好吃的
Goodies!
我杀了她
I killed her.
不算
Not...quite.
肉身早就死了
The meat suit was already dead.
是里面的灵魂维系了它的生命
It was just the soul that was inside it that was keeping it alive.
现在没了
Not anymore.
谢谢你  克劳力叔叔
Thank you, uncle Crowley.
不客气
You're welcome.
去机场
Airport.
小心拿包  都是古董
And be careful with the bags. They're antiquities.
[咒语]
我就这样冲你竖手指  温彻斯特先生
Just my way of giving you the finger... Mr. Winchester.
你估计不是来
I don't suppose you're here
感谢我帮你祛除了该隐血印的吧
to thank me for removing the Mark of Cain,
对了  不客气哦
which, by the way, you're welcome.
我们再上个台阶吧
Let's just take things up a notch.
怎么样
What do you say?
你现在该知道了  萨穆埃尔
I think you'd know by now, Samuel,
这些东西困不住我多久
these things don't hold me long.
我只需要困住你足够长的时间
I just need to hold you long enough.
早听说金发更好玩
Well, they do say blondes have more fun.
想查一辆车的信息
"To pull up information on a car,
选择搜索框
select search box,
输入违法行为
type in violations.
再输入车牌号
And enter license plate number,
车型
make..."
幸运交配
Fortune nookie,
亚裔女孩性幻想首选网站
your premiere web site for all your Asian girl fantasies.
我们有几百位美丽的女孩
We have hundreds of lovely girls
就等着跟你聊天呢
just waiting to chat with you
全天候恭候
24 hours a day.
幸运交配什么意思啊
What could "Fortune Nookie" be?
[咒语]
卡西迪奥
Castiel...
不要
Don't!
[咒语]
餐厅里在上死肉身吧
Cafeteria is serving dead meat suits, right?
是的  陛下
Yes, majesty.
不会有没魂的疯子在走廊里乱跑
No chance of soulless lunatics roaming the halls.
有人提到甜点了吗
Did I hear someone mention dessert?
稍等  亲爱的
In a minute, sweetheart.
我们刚刚说到哪了
Now, what were we just chatting about?
上帝创造人类时  完全搞砸了
How when God created mankind, he really screwed it up.
注意语言哦
Language!
原始力量哪能这么说话
Is that any way for a primal force to speak?
我每次吸食一个灵魂
Every time I take in a soul,
都能深深感到空洞感
I feel how much emptiness there is.
是啊
Yes.
上帝创造了一个让人类受苦
God made a world where people have to suffer,
死去的世界
and then they die.
-真是不幸  -但老实说
- Unfortunately. - But Frankly,
他们为什么要活在这样的世界上啊
why would they want to live in such a world?
我向你的真知灼见致敬  亲亲
I salute your insight, cupcake.
是啊  上帝的计划有很大缺陷
Yes, God's plan is hideously flawed.
但你我联手
But you and I together?
我们可以按照自己的想法塑造世界
Well, we can shape things to our own world view.
一个美德像恐龙一样
A place where, like the dinosaur,
灭绝
virtue is extinct,
空气中都是绝对邪恶的味道的世界
where the very air that we breathe is pure evil.
你喜欢那样吗
Would you like that?
你呢
Would you?
如果大家都是邪恶的
You'd really be happy if everyone...
你真就开心了吗
was evil?
其实  想起来
Well...actually, now I come to think of it,
如果人人都黑暗  被诅咒
if everyone was dark and damned,
就不怎么具有挑战性了
wouldn't be much of a challenge.
看着人类拒绝光明
Watching a human reject the light
拥抱堕落  那才
and embrace depravity... yes, well,
能给人满足感
that's where the gratification really is.
从不会觉得无聊
Never gets old.
你觉得困惑吗
This bemuses you?
好  坏  天堂  地狱  人类
Good, evil, heaven, hell, people..
一切都感觉好渺小
It all seems so unimportant.
也未必吧
Well, I don't know that I'd say that.
我觉得你没看到大局
I don't think you're seeing the big picture.
什么意思
Meaning what exactly?
猜怎么着  克劳力叔叔
Guess what, uncle Crowley?
我饿了
I'm hungry.
不
No.
内衣小心点拿  萨穆埃尔
Mind the undergarments, Samuel.
都是进口的
Imported, of course.
在哪
Where is it?
什么在哪
Where is what, dear?
那本书
The book!
《诅咒之书》
The Book of the Damned.
法典在里面  但书不在
The codex is in there, but the book is not.
书在哪
So where the hell is it?
你当我是傻瓜吗
Do you take me for a fool?
我会随身带着那两件非凡的宝器
Like I'd run around with those two spectacularly powerful items
把他们放在一起吗
anywhere in proximity.
那我们拿到法典了
Well, now we've got the codex
还有查理的解码
and Charlie's code-breaking,
所以那本书对你也不像之前那么有用了
so the book isn't as useful to you as it was.
你是希望如此吧
Or so you hope.
我就钦佩你这点  萨穆埃尔
That's what I admire in you, Samuel.
这种大胆的乐观主义
That plucky optimism.
大胆愚蠢的乐观主义
That plucky, stupid optimism.
萨姆  你去找小卡来
Sam, why don't you go grab Cass
让红发天使做她该做的
so Florence Nightingale here can do her stuff?
嗯
Yeah.
你记得我们的协议吧
You do recall our deal, eh?
我解除天使的咒语  然后放我走
First I de-spell the angel, then I go free.
除了一件事
Mm, except for one thing.
我们的协议没有例外
There were no exceptions in our arrangement.
书  那个得拿回来
The book. Gonna need that baby back.
我们的协议里没提到书
The book was never mentioned in our negotiations.
现在有了
Well, now it is.
我们的协议是
Our deal says...
我们的协议我说什么就是什么
Our deal says whatever I want it to say.
你要按我的规矩来
You're gonna play by my rules
因为你儿子的电话我一键就能拨通
because I have your son on speed dial.
打给他啊
Call him.
如果我死了  你就什么都别想得到
If I'm dead, you've got a big fat pile of nothing.
永远别想拿到书了
No book ever.
你那个光环坏掉的朋友
And your friend with the bent halo?
他会疯到口吐白沫死掉
He goes foaming-at-the-mouth mad and dies.
该你了
Your turn!
你的眼睛
Your eyes...
背负重担
So burdened.
我祛除了血印后发生了什么
What happened precisely when I removed the mark?
书里没细说
The book wasn't specific.
我是读了不少
Yes, I read quite a bit of it.
迪恩·温彻斯特又往这世界上释放了
What new hell has Dean Winchester unleashed
什么新灾难
upon the world?
-迪恩  -怎么
- Dean! - Yeah?
我找不到小卡
Hey, I can't find Cass.
-什么  -他不在  他挣脱了
- What? - He's not there. He... he... he broke free.
他不见了
He's gone.
真荒谬  开车到处兜圈找你们的落跑天使
So absurd, driving in circles looking for your unhinged angel.
我们没在兜圈
We're not driving in circles, all right?
我们锁定了他的手机GPS
We're locked onto his phone's G.P.S.
正在追踪他的位置
We're tracking his location.
我完全听不懂你刚刚说的话
I have no idea what you just said,
但我肯定能做得更快
but I'm sure I could do it faster.
或许吧
Yeah, maybe you could,
但那样你就得施咒了
but you would have to do a spell,
我们就得给你解下手铐
which means we would have to take the cuffs off,
那是不可能的
and we are not going to take the cuffs off.
毫无信任吗  我们不是一个团队吗
There's no trust? Are we not a team?
不是
No.
您找我  陛下
You sent for me, sire?
我想表扬你
I wanted to commend you
在前任因不适离职后
for how well you've stepped into your new role as nanny
很好地接替了保姆一职
after the last one became indisposed.
不适  她死了
"Indisposed"? She's dead.
总之  你似乎很适合这种工作
At any rate, you seem to be cut out for this kind of work.
阿玛拉显然很喜欢你
Amara clearly responds to you.
她像看食物一样看着我
She looks at me like she wants to eat me.
她看什么都像食物  别往心里去
She wants to eat everyone. Don't take it personally.
陛下  我没有带孩子的经验
Majesty, uh, I have no experience with children.
我不能做别的吗
Um, is there nothing else I can do?
看来是不能
Apparently not,
毕竟你没能刺杀我母亲
seeing as you failed to assassinate my mother.
我可不想再失望
I'd hate to be disappointed twice.
我知道
I'm aware.
是这样的
So, here's the thing.
阿玛拉似乎长得很快
Amara seems to be growing in leaps and bounds.
不仅是成熟度
Not just in maturity,
力量和自信都大涨
but in strength and confidence, too.
我不希望她失控
I don't want her to get out of hand
我还不能确信她的忠心
before I'm sure of her loyalty.
你要停止对她的无度喂食
I need you to stop overfeeding her.
但您说要满足她的一切要求的
But you said to give her whatever she wants
不论她何时需要
whenever she wants it.
现在我改说法了
Well, now I'm saying something different, aren't I?
是
Yes.
可不能培养出自以为是的
We don't want a generation of entitled,
小胖丫头啊
pudgy kids, do we?
当然不了
No, we do not.
告诉她
So simple inform her
我们要减少她的灵魂食物
that we're cutting back on her soul food.
这样更加健康
It's, uh, it's the healthier choice.
您要我去跟她说吗
You want me to tell her this?
你不是她的保姆吗
You are her nanny, aren't you?
-这...  -如果你不是
- Well... - 'cause if you're not the nanny,
那你是什么
then what are you?
我知道了
Oh, I know...
插在竿子上  烤到时间尽头
roasting on a spit until the end of time.
我尽力吧
I'll, uh, do my best.
很好
Good man.
你系围裙真好看
And you look wonderful in an apron.
(卡西迪奥)
跟两个这么高大威猛的小伙子一起公路旅行
You wouldn't think a road trip with two such strapping lads
居然能这么无聊
could be this tedious.
我们唱唱歌吧
Shall we have a wee sing-song?
不行
No!
只能怪我自己
I have myself to blame.
就不该跟温家人做协议
Should never make deals with Winchesters,
他们似乎从来不能履行协议
since they seem unable to hold up their end of the bargain.
什么意思
Meaning what?
就是萨姆  克劳力和我之间的那件事
Oh, just that thing between Sam, Crowley, and myself.
什么  她在说什么
What? What's she talking about?
你肯定是知道萨姆跟我做了协议  他杀我儿子
Oh, surely, you knew Sam made a deal with me to kill my son
交换我祛除你胳膊上的该隐血印吧
if I removed the Mark of Cain from your arm.
血印祛除了吗  是的
Well, is the mark gone? Yes.
克劳力死了吗  没有
Is Crowley dead? No.
他不知道吗
Oh, he didn't know?
他不知道诶
He didn't know!
我想告诉你的
Look, I was gonna tell you.
不用说  那事最终无果
Obviously, nothing ever came of it,
我就觉得没那个必要了
so I-I figured there was no point, you know?
没必要
No point, huh?
我明白迪恩的意思
I-I mean, I see what Dean's saying.
如果你遵守了承诺
Your wee pal Castiel wouldn't be in this pickle
你的朋友卡西迪奥就不会陷入这麻烦了
if you'd done what you'd promised.
如果克劳力已经死了
I would've had no reason to cast the attack dog spell
我也没必要施下疯狗咒
if Crowley were already dead.
说得好
Excellent point.
我没那么想
It's not my point.
萨姆知道我怎么想
Sam knows my point.
关键词是秘密
Keyword... secrets.
我很高兴我们聊起来了
Ah, well, I'm just glad I got the conversation flowing.
家庭关系我最擅长了
Family relations are a speciality of mine.
-他停下了吗  -嗯  是的
- Did he stop? - Yeah, he stopped.
(卡西迪奥)
他就在附近
And he's close.
走吧
Come on.
他肯定就在附近
All right, he's gotta be around here somewhere.
我往前走  你们走另一边
So I'll head up the street, you guys head the other way.
开玩笑吗  我穿着高跟呢
Are you joking? I'm in heels.
干点正事儿吧
Get a life.
小卡  小卡
Cass! Cass!
别这样
Don't do this.
这不是你  是咒语的影响
Okay, this isn't you. It's the spell.
你能克服的
You can beat this.
小卡...
Cass...
放开她
Let her go.
快走  快走
Go, go, go, go.
好了  好了
Okay, okay.
会没事的  兄弟  好吗
It's gonna be okay, buddy, all right?
[咒语]
需要我提醒你这是杀女巫的子弹吗
Do I need to remind you these are witch-killing bullets?
把咒语终结了
Finish it!
好啦  知道了
Yes, yes, all right.
[咒语]
小卡
Cass?
来吧  起来
Come on. Come on.
好了
Yeah.
[咒语]
不
No!
[咒语]
我确信你绝对有意遵守我们的约定
I'm sure you had every intention of honoring our deal.
但何必冒险呢
But why take chances?
你应该继续敷着
You should keep applying that.
谢了  老妈  你只管一直上啤酒就好
Thanks, mom. You just keep the beers comin'.
迪恩  我...
Dean, I...
我的心情言语无法表达
There aren't words.
你说得对  是没什么可说的  小卡
You're right. There aren't words, Cass,
因为没这个必要
'cause there's no need.
你是被咒语控制了  没关系的
You were under a spell. It's fine.
是啊  但你们都抓到罗威娜了
Yeah, but you had Rowena.
因为我  你们...
Because of me, you...
你知道吗  小卡
You know, Cass,
我们拿到法典了
we've got the codex.
这是个开头  这能稍稍减慢罗威娜的速度
That's a start. You know, it'll slow Rowena down some.
假如我们杀了她
If we'd killed her,
就永远也找不到《诅咒之书》了
The Book of The Damned would've been lost.
另外  我们还有更要紧的事要操心
Besides, we got bigger fish to fry.
黑暗
The darkness.
她想要什么
What does she want?
最大的问题是  她现在在哪
Well, the big question is, where the hell is she?
迪恩  我能治好你
Dean, I can fix that.
不不  没关系的  小卡
No, no, no. No, no. It's fine, Cass.
再说了  我也是该打
Besides, I had it comin'.
特此下令...等等等等
Hereby command and decree... blah, blah, blah.
永生永世被挂在钩子上...
Hung on hooks for all eternity...
内脏挖走...
Entrails removed...
阿玛拉
Amara?
我饿了
I'm hungry.
当然了  小乖乖
Of course, poppet.
但这样吧  也许我们应该先聊聊
But tell you what, maybe we should have a chat first.
我说了
I said
我饿了
I'm hungry.